<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>quangtiencs</title>
    <link>https://quangtiencs.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on quangtiencs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>quangtiencs ➤ bet on myself &amp; beat the odds</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quangtiencs.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://quangtiencs.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quangtiencs.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, this is quangtiencs’s log, a homepage of my engineering life. I am Tien Le-Quang (Lê Quang Tiến), a data detective (a.k.a data scientist). I decided to start writing down my learning notes when I developed or learned something new. As a critical-thinking practitioner, my opinions are always subject to rethinking and revision. If you find any mistakes, please do not hesitate to give me feedback.
With a lifelong learning mindset, I am on the road to becoming a magical statistician, a world-class engineer, and such a fantastic father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rửa chén</title>
      <link>https://quangtiencs.com/vietnam/rua_chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quangtiencs.com/vietnam/rua_chen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;mỗi lần say mê rửa chén là lại nghĩ ra cái gì đó hay ho. Hóa ra, khi đôi bàn tay ta làm những việc thật &amp;ldquo;khủng khiếp&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;nhem nhuốc&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;dơ bẩn&amp;rdquo; là nơi của mọi thứ bắt đầu&amp;hellip; cả thế giới to đùng bỗng chốc thu bé lại chỉ bằng mấy cái chén chưa rửa xong&amp;hellip;
Giờ chẳng nhẽ nhận thêm việc rửa chén bán thời gian cho tăng năng suất công việc nhỉ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Đặt cược</title>
      <link>https://quangtiencs.com/vietnam/dat_cuoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quangtiencs.com/vietnam/dat_cuoc/</guid>
      <description>Bet on myself and beat the odds.
&amp;hellip;liệu em có thể yêu một gã đánh bạc như anh?
Đặt cược tất cả vào bản thân mình&amp;hellip; để chiến đấu với mọi thử thách.
Có / Không thôi nhé? Đây là một câu hỏi khó &amp;amp; cần một lời giải chân phương&amp;hellip;
Lê Quang Tiến - viết vào ngày 23 tháng 09 năm 2020</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
